<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dkas Consulting</title>
    <link>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dkas Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OpenVSP Workshop Presentation</title>
      <link>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/posts/vsp_conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/posts/vsp_conference/</guid>
      <description>Greetings!
Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to share with you a joint presentation that I did with Dr Vivek Ahuja from Research in Flight for the 2022 OpenVSP Workshop, held in the National Institute of Aerospace (Virginia).
The presentation focuses on the latest developments in Flightstream, including the CCS format and how that is significantly improving the experience of using Flightstream. As a part of this work and to facilitate a greater connection between Flightstream &amp;amp; OpenVSP, I have created a simple software utility that converts an OpenVSP model into a useable Flightstream CCS file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 01:49:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>OpenVSP to FlightStream Model Conversion UtilityLink to headingThis utility by DKAS Consulting allows you to quickly &amp;amp; easily convert your VSP model into a FlightStream ready CCS File. The CCS file can be imported to FlightStream with 1-click, and allows you to quickly and easily define mesh refinement &amp;amp; control surfaces.
Free Version: Download
Premium Version: Coming Soon.
Planned Features:
Config file to save parameters for each aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>DKAS ConsultingLink to headingDKAS Consulting is the brain-child of Daniel Kassabian &amp;amp; offers consulting services related to aerodynamics &amp;amp; aircraft CFD, Flight Simulation Development as well as general programming consultation.
Dan, along with his brother Alex, founded FlyingIron Simulations in 2018 and the company has become a stalwart in the Flight Sim community, with several aircraft released across multiple simulation platforms.
Daniel Kassabian &amp;amp; DKAS Consulting has worked on various simulators &amp;amp; projects since 2018, including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Thank you for visiting my personal website.
Although there isn&amp;rsquo;t a great deal of content here, I&amp;rsquo;ve created this website to not only share some of my development creations that others may find useful, but also as a point of contact should anybody out there require my services.
I hope you find something here useful!
Thank you,
Dan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://DanFlyingIronSims.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>For questions, enquiries &amp;amp; bookings reach out to me at: Dan@dkasconsulting.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
