<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DKAS Consulting</title>
    <link>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DKAS Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 01:32:49 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VSP to Flightstream Utility - Instructions</title>
      <link>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/vsp_utility_instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 01:32:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/vsp_utility_instructions/</guid>
      <description>Under Construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DCS World Joystick Setup Tool (For Devs)</title>
      <link>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/dcs_joystick_utility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/dcs_joystick_utility/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
Today I&amp;rsquo;m sharing a very simple tool that may be useful for other DCS World developers.
It is a simple python script that automates the creation of your aircrafts joystick input lua file, so that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to make it twice. It does this by copying your keyboard lua setup file.
To use the script, simply place it in your DCS modules input/keyboard folder and run it.
Get it here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenVSP Workshop Presentation</title>
      <link>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/vsp_conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/vsp_conference/</guid>
      <description>Greetings!
Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to share with you a joint presentation that I did with Dr Vivek Ahuja from Research in Flight for the 2022 OpenVSP Workshop, held in the National Institute of Aerospace (Virginia).
The presentation focuses on the latest developments in Flightstream, including the CCS format and how that is significantly improving the experience of using Flightstream. As a part of this work and to facilitate a greater connection between Flightstream &amp;amp; OpenVSP, I have created a simple software utility that converts an OpenVSP model into a useable Flightstream CCS file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dkasconsulting.com/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Thank you for visiting my personal website.
Although there isn&amp;rsquo;t a great deal of content here, I&amp;rsquo;ve created this website to not only share some of my development creations that others may find useful, but also as a point of contact should anybody out there require my services.
I hope you find something here useful!
Thank you,
Dan</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
